http://www.degrees-online.com/privacy.html

Degrees Onlinewww.degrees-online.com
Privacy Policy
The following is a disclosure of Degrees-Online's privacy practices on this site.
No Personally Identifiable Information
This site does not collect any personally identifying information about individuals visiting this site, such as name, address, telephone number or email address.
Occasionally anonymous aggregated data, such as collective user domain names and referring URLs identified by our server logs, is analyzed.
This is done only for internal purposes, either to compile traffic analyses for our site or to email inquiries generated from our site.
Our web server does not have the capability to recognize your name, email addresses or any personally identifiable information, and thus we do not have access to this information.
External Links
This site contains links to other Websites, all of which operate by their own separate privacy policies, and over which we have no control, and for which we are not responsible.
We encourage you to familiarize yourself with the privacy policies of every site you visit, particularly before disclosing any sort of personally identifiable information about yourself.
Advertising
This site sometimes displays advertising from advertisers, such as Google's AdWords program, who sometimes make use of cookies or similar tracking technologies in their ads appearing on our site.
If they exist, they are being served from the advertiser, and we do not have access to or control over any information they may collect.
Degrees-Online uses no cookies or similar tracking technologies of any kind.
As technology on the Internet is developing at a rapid pace, we need to maintain our flexibility in the online arena. If we need to change our policy in the future, we will post these changes as soon as they go into effect.
Degrees-Online.com
